Guide to the United States Labor Education in the Americas Project (L.E.A.P) records, "1983-2013 LAC0016
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audio, Digital and Video Recordings, 1993-2009; Series 8
  - "Globalization Panel Women's Conference"-Pictures- CD, September 13, 2008; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 6)
  - "Gloria's Back-Up disk 2" CD, April 2003; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 7)
  - "GSP"-Floppy Disks, 1994-2001; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 8)
  - "IBC II" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 9)
  - "Imports"-Floppy Disks, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - "Impunity in Colombia-Yessika Hoyos Tour" CD, September 30, 2009; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - "Informe Nacional de Desarrollo Humano-ASDI" CD, 2003; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 12)
  - "Informes Derechos Humanos-ENS/E.U." CDs, 2006; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 13)
  - "ITGLWF-Stop Aids!" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 14)
  - "John Gaige Letter" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 15)
  - "Justice for All: A Guide to Workers Rights in the Global Economy" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 16)
  - "Juzgados Penales del Circuito Especializados" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 17)
  - "Labor Express" CDs, November 7-14, 2004; Series 8 (Box 213, Folder 18)
  - "Letters"-Floppy disks, 2002; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 1)
  - "Maquila"-Floppy disks, 1994-1997; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 2)
  - "Members"-Floppy disks, 1995-2002; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 3)
  - Miscellanous Floppy Disks, 1997-2001; Series 8 (Flat box 217)
  - "My Docs"-Back-up CDs, 2004-2005; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - "Newsletters/Press"-Floppy Disks, 1999-2001; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 5)
  - "Nicaragua"-Floppy Disks, undated; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 6)
  - "PN"-Floppy Disks, undated; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 7)
  - "Precarious Peace-God and Guatemala"-CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 8)
  - "PVH"-Floppy Disks, 1994-1999; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 9)
  - "Q&A"-Floppy Disks, 1996-2001; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 10)
  - "Quicken"-Floppy Disks, 2003; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 11)
  - "Propuesto de Convenio-Uito, Colsiba, y TransFair-USA" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 12)
  - "Research"-Floppy Disks, 1999; Series 8 (Box 214, Folder 13)
  - "Rubie's/Mattel" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - "Sentencias Violencia AntiSindical/Fiscalia Reports" Cds" CD, 2002-2010; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 2)
  - "SEIU Presentation 2004" CD, Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 3)
  - "SintraDepartamento Conflicto Laboral-Ingles" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 4)
  - "Stuff Vol.2.2" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 5)
  - "Travel Disks"-Floppy Disks, 1998; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 6)
  - "Triplex"-Floppy Disks, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 7)
  - "Todxs Queremos llegar a casa"-Music CD, May 2008; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 8)
  - "UNITE Presentation" CD, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 9)
  - "USAS Organizing CD", February. 2002; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 10)
  - "USLEAP July 2003 Newlsetter" CDs", Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 11)
  - "USLEAP webpage/website Design" CDs, undated; Series 8 (Box 215, Folder 12)
  - USLEAP Video/Audio Cassettes", 1994-2004; Series 8 (Box 216)
  - Zip 100 MB Disks [1/5], 2000-2001; Series 8 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Zip 100 MB Disks [2/5], 2001-2002; Series 8 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Zip 100 MB Disks [3/5], 2001-2002; Series 8 (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Zip 100 MB Disks [4/5], 2001-2002; Series 8 (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Zip 100 MB Disks [5/5], 2002; Series 8 (Box 219, Folder 5)